const quizArr = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the first pillar of Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "Salah (Prayer)",
      B: "Zakat (Charity)",
      C: "Shahada (Faith)",
      D: "Sawm (Fasting)",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "What does 'Zakat' refer to in Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "Fasting during Ramadan",
      B: "The pilgrimage to Mecca",
      C: "Obligatory charity",
      D: "Daily prayers",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which book is considered the holy scripture of Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "The Bible",
      B: "The Torah",
      C: "The Quran",
      D: "The Hadith",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the significance of the Hadith in Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "It is the book of prayers.",
      B: "It contains the sayings and actions of Prophet Muhammad.",
      C: "It is a collection of historical events.",
      D: "It is a book of laws.",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "What is the meaning of 'Salah'?",
    options: {
      A: "Charity",
      B: "Fasting",
      C: "Prayer",
      D: "Faith",
    },
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "What is the purpose of fasting during Ramadan?",
    options: {
      A: "To lose weight",
      B: "To develop self-discipline and empathy for the less fortunate",
      C: "To socialize with friends",
      D: "To gain wealth",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What is the term for the pilgrimage to Mecca that Muslims must perform at least once in their lifetime?",
    options: {
      A: "Zakat",
      B: "Hajj",
      C: "Umrah",
      D: "Salah",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT one of the six articles of faith in Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "Belief in Allah",
      B: "Belief in angels",
      C: "Belief in the afterlife",
      D: "Belief in reincarnation",
    },
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What is the significance of the month of Ramadan in Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "It is the month of Hajj.",
      B: "It is the month of fasting and spiritual reflection.",
      C: "It is the month of charity.",
      D: "It is the month of pilgrimage.",
    },
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What does the term 'Ummah' refer to in Islam?",
    options: {
      A: "The community of believers",
      B: "The holy book",
      C: "The prayer",
      D: "The pilgrimage",
    },
    answer: "A",
  },
];

